So diagonal first
stock which out performs then this was
PVR
ji support level which is source of science Osho
and Satyanaj is a support level
last video from elephant when strong pull back is enough
many tomorrow a strong positive formations
come close up I will have kind of a double
bottle formation a reversal we are
trying then pvruk counter a if
we hit the lamp in the market which is
177062 levelli around if the account model
is 7062 around in our account the
password is
₹30 on target
like this ICICI General Insurance
positive market negative
moving average
selling price and open on the same side our
short position built upli sixth which is our gauge
so again
show 40 not level not around if we
want model then I can build up short in my account
which is ₹1100 on openings app so I have placed
stop on down side
1000 new shruti target on down side
experiment do long not short
Opportunity will be initiated when because the
market is overall ranging from today,
in stock specific action you are both long and
short side then I will see the trading
action outside